<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Software on Strange Labs Computers</title>
    <link>https://strangelabs.io/tags/software/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Software on Strange Labs Computers</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://strangelabs.io/tags/software/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Genius Gaming Tales- Creative Exploits and Strategies</title>
      <link>https://strangelabs.io/blog/genius-gaming-tales/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://strangelabs.io/blog/genius-gaming-tales/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Gaming is great, but what&amp;rsquo;s truly fascinating is when players devise ingenious plans to &amp;ldquo;hack&amp;rdquo; the game using nothing but the engine itself. No cheats, no actual hacking, just pure, creative strategy. These approaches not only showcase the ability to &amp;ldquo;win&amp;rdquo; by exploiting unintended game mechanics but also offer intriguing insights into the psychology of the gamers themselves.&#xA;Let&amp;rsquo;s explore some of the most captivating examples of strategic exploits in simulation games.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Think In A World Of Cybercrime</title>
      <link>https://strangelabs.io/blog/how-to-think-in-a-world-of-cybercrime/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://strangelabs.io/blog/how-to-think-in-a-world-of-cybercrime/</guid>
      <description>Introduction As technology and networking become increasingly integrated into our lives, the threat of cybercrime will only grow. It&amp;rsquo;s a scary reality, and if you find yourself feeling paranoid, you&amp;rsquo;re probably justified. In this article, I&amp;rsquo;ll share how I approach this complex digital landscape and offer some advice on how you might want to think about it too. Be warned, this perspective isn&amp;rsquo;t for the faint of heart.&#xA;The Escalating Cyber Threat In recent years, we’ve been bombarded with news about cyber attacks, ransomware infections, and data breaches.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strengthening Relationships Weakened By The Internet</title>
      <link>https://strangelabs.io/blog/strengthening-relationships-weakened-by-the-internet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://strangelabs.io/blog/strengthening-relationships-weakened-by-the-internet/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Back in 2003, whilst I was a teenager, I found myself rebelling against the idea of owning a mobile phone. Something about it just didn’t sit right with me. I think that I sensed a future where increased social connections would lead to each one feeling less meaningful. Or maybe it was simply the reluctance to be available 24/7. I cherished the ritual of asking my parents to use the house phone, ensuring no one was online, and then calling a friend’s landline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Speed Up Your Windows 10 Startup</title>
      <link>https://strangelabs.io/guides/speeding-up-windows-10-startup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://strangelabs.io/guides/speeding-up-windows-10-startup/</guid>
      <description>Hardware Upgrades The easiest, though often most expensive, method to boost your PC&amp;rsquo;s performance is by upgrading the hardware. One of the most impactful upgrades you can make is adding a Solid State Drive (SSD). Unlike traditional mechanical Hard Disk Drives (HDDs), SSDs have no moving parts and offer read and write speeds that are significantly faster. Opting for an NVMe SSD can further enhance speed, as these drives utilise a faster interface than the standard SATA protocol.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Full Stack Buildings Design</title>
      <link>https://strangelabs.io/blog/full-stack-buildings-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://strangelabs.io/blog/full-stack-buildings-design/</guid>
      <description>Designing Buildings in the Future The future of architecture is evolving, giving rise to a new breed of architects with broader vision, deeper influence, and a more comprehensive understanding of their craft. These future architects won’t just design buildings in the traditional sense, from material selection to philosophical considerations, but will also grasp the intricacies of modern technology. They will understand everything from the flow of electrons in wiring to the connectivity of the internet, and how these elements interact with the building&amp;rsquo;s users in an increasingly digital world.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
