<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gaming on Strange Labs Computers</title>
    <link>https://strangelabs.io/tags/gaming/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gaming on Strange Labs Computers</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://strangelabs.io/tags/gaming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Genius Gaming Tales- Creative Exploits and Strategies</title>
      <link>https://strangelabs.io/blog/genius-gaming-tales/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://strangelabs.io/blog/genius-gaming-tales/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Gaming is great, but what&amp;rsquo;s truly fascinating is when players devise ingenious plans to &amp;ldquo;hack&amp;rdquo; the game using nothing but the engine itself. No cheats, no actual hacking, just pure, creative strategy. These approaches not only showcase the ability to &amp;ldquo;win&amp;rdquo; by exploiting unintended game mechanics but also offer intriguing insights into the psychology of the gamers themselves.&#xA;Let&amp;rsquo;s explore some of the most captivating examples of strategic exploits in simulation games.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EGX Rezzed 2019 - Our most interesting picks!</title>
      <link>https://strangelabs.io/blog/egx-rezzed-2019-best-of-the-bunch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://strangelabs.io/blog/egx-rezzed-2019-best-of-the-bunch/</guid>
      <description>EGX Rezzed, London’s biggest gaming event, concluded a week ago. Strange Labs was in attendance and amongst the various qualities of cosplayers wandering around, excellent merchandise and endless games to play, there were also some pretty cool talks from the developers themselves. We managed to get to a few (annoyingly everything inevitably overlaps at these sorts of events) and thought we would share our favourite picks of brand new, up and coming games.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Louqe Ghost S1 - Case Review</title>
      <link>https://strangelabs.io/guides/louqe-ghost-s1-case-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://strangelabs.io/guides/louqe-ghost-s1-case-review/</guid>
      <description>Building in the Louqe Ghost S1: A Compact ITX Marvel The Louqe Ghost S1 is a masterpiece of design for those seeking the smallest possible ITX build without compromising on airflow or temperatures. At Strange Labs, we&amp;rsquo;ve always had a soft spot for small PCs, and the ITX form factor holds a special place in our hearts. Our everyday PC resides in a Bitfenix Portal, one of the more intriguing cases out there.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
