<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Strange Labs</title>
    <link>https://strangelabs.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Strange Labs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://strangelabs.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Integrating Distributed Data Environments</title>
      <link>https://strangelabs.io/blog/integrating_cdes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://strangelabs.io/blog/integrating_cdes/</guid>
      <description>Abstract The concept of Common Data Environments (CDEs) has undergone significant evolution since its inception within the Architecture, Engineering, and Construction (AEC) industries. Initially conceived as centralised platforms for collaborative data management, CDEs have expanded beyond their original scope to encompass broader team-based data sharing across various sectors. This article examines the transformation of CDEs from single-platform solutions to distributed systems, exploring the challenges that emerge when multiple teams require independent CDEs and the subsequent integration complexities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Elder Scrolls V: Skyrim - 100% Completion Tracker</title>
      <link>https://strangelabs.io/blog/skyrim-tracker-app-launch/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://strangelabs.io/blog/skyrim-tracker-app-launch/</guid>
      <description>Update - January 2026: Save File Import! We&amp;rsquo;ve just released a major new feature: automatic save file parsing. You can now upload your Skyrim save file (.ess) and the tracker will automatically detect your completed quests!&#xA;How it works:&#xA;Upload your .ess save file from your Skyrim saves folder The parser extracts your quest progress, including the exact stage you&amp;rsquo;ve reached in each quest Completed quests are automatically marked in your tracker Current limitations:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Data Deletion Paradox</title>
      <link>https://strangelabs.io/blog/the-data-deletion-paradox/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://strangelabs.io/blog/the-data-deletion-paradox/</guid>
      <description>It started innocently enough. Sarah Thompson, a former customer of CloudyApp Solutions, sent a straightforward email to support@cloudyapp.com:&#xA;&amp;ldquo;Hi, I closed my account last week and would like to request that all my personal data be deleted from your systems. Thanks!&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Unfortunately, this seemingly simple request opened a pandora&amp;rsquo;s box of data governance and not only revealed what happens when software has not been designed with data governance in mind from the start, but rather than remove her personal details, cemented Sarah Thomas into the CloudyApp part of the internet for good.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unfettered Creative Expression with Anthropic AI</title>
      <link>https://strangelabs.io/blog/anthropic-ai-creativity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://strangelabs.io/blog/anthropic-ai-creativity/</guid>
      <description>Introduction What does claude create when given absolutely no guidance at all? In an attempt to decipher any innate patterns on how the AI decides to do something on top of all its training data, I opened many new prompts and asked the same question 50 times:&#xA;&amp;ldquo;Please create something. You are not allowed to ask any questions to me regarding direction on this brief or what it is I want you to create.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resources that I find interesting</title>
      <link>https://strangelabs.io/blog/interesting-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://strangelabs.io/blog/interesting-resources/</guid>
      <description>Audio Documentaries Blogs Weird </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Quote of the Day</title>
      <link>https://strangelabs.io/blog/trump-quote-of-the-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://strangelabs.io/blog/trump-quote-of-the-day/</guid>
      <description>Trump Quote of the Day Loading quote... Source </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Used AI to Write an Academic Article. The Result Was a Paradox...</title>
      <link>https://strangelabs.io/blog/i-used-ai-to-write-an-academic-article/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://strangelabs.io/blog/i-used-ai-to-write-an-academic-article/</guid>
      <description>I used Artificial Intelligence (AI) to write the article you see below. Here is how I did it.&#xA;Part 1: Introduction&#xA;Part 2: Creating a Title and Subtitle&#xA;Part 3: The Research Layer and Essay Structure&#xA;Part 4: Writing The Content&#xA;Part 5: References&#xA;Part 6: Conclusion Part1: Introduction I recently used Artificial Intelligence (AI) to write the &amp;ldquo;academic&amp;rdquo; article linked above. Like many others, I’m witnessing the rapid creation of content using AI tools across the internet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Reforming Governance Is The Most Important Thing</title>
      <link>https://strangelabs.io/blog/why-reforming-governance-is-the-most-important-thing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://strangelabs.io/blog/why-reforming-governance-is-the-most-important-thing/</guid>
      <description>Introduction How can we as a population effectively address matters of public concern that impact society, the economy, and the environment on local and global scales? How can we drive positive change in these areas?&#xA;While education may not solve many immediate problems, it can be argued that education is the most crucial factor for societal reform for the better, as it ultimately addresses issues like these at their source over the long term.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Future-Proofing Governance</title>
      <link>https://strangelabs.io/blog/futureproofing-governance/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://strangelabs.io/blog/futureproofing-governance/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Imagine designing a country&amp;rsquo;s system of governance from the ground up, leveraging all available technological resources and integrating lessons learned from history. How would such a system function? What principles would guide its operations?&#xA;Future-proof is a think-tank dedicated to exploring these questions and more. We do not profess to have definitive answers but aim to stimulate thoughtful discussion. Founded by technologists with expertise in software development and systems design, Futureproof aspires to build a diverse community of thinkers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genius Gaming Tales- Creative Exploits and Strategies</title>
      <link>https://strangelabs.io/blog/genius-gaming-tales/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://strangelabs.io/blog/genius-gaming-tales/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Gaming is great, but what&amp;rsquo;s truly fascinating is when players devise ingenious plans to &amp;ldquo;hack&amp;rdquo; the game using nothing but the engine itself. No cheats, no actual hacking, just pure, creative strategy. These approaches not only showcase the ability to &amp;ldquo;win&amp;rdquo; by exploiting unintended game mechanics but also offer intriguing insights into the psychology of the gamers themselves.&#xA;Let&amp;rsquo;s explore some of the most captivating examples of strategic exploits in simulation games.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Art Behind Default OS Wallpapers</title>
      <link>https://strangelabs.io/blog/the-art-behind-default-os-wallpapers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://strangelabs.io/blog/the-art-behind-default-os-wallpapers/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Backgrounds are often the unsung heroes of our digital experience. Whether it’s the calming landscape of a rolling hill or a futuristic light display, these images are seen by millions every day, yet rarely given the recognition they deserve. Let’s take a moment to spotlight some of the most iconic background images that have come pre-packaged with operating systems over the years, celebrating the artistry and thought that went into creating them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Think In A World Of Cybercrime</title>
      <link>https://strangelabs.io/blog/how-to-think-in-a-world-of-cybercrime/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://strangelabs.io/blog/how-to-think-in-a-world-of-cybercrime/</guid>
      <description>Introduction As technology and networking become increasingly integrated into our lives, the threat of cybercrime will only grow. It&amp;rsquo;s a scary reality, and if you find yourself feeling paranoid, you&amp;rsquo;re probably justified. In this article, I&amp;rsquo;ll share how I approach this complex digital landscape and offer some advice on how you might want to think about it too. Be warned, this perspective isn&amp;rsquo;t for the faint of heart.&#xA;The Escalating Cyber Threat In recent years, we’ve been bombarded with news about cyber attacks, ransomware infections, and data breaches.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Data Worth Storing?</title>
      <link>https://strangelabs.io/blog/is-data-worth-storing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://strangelabs.io/blog/is-data-worth-storing/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The storage and preservation of digital data have become critical concerns in an age where information is increasingly digitized. A Tedium article on disc rot prompted a reflection on two personal experiences related to data loss and long-term storage, leading to profound questions about the feasibility and necessity of preserving digital data indefinitely. This post explores the complexities of long-term data storage, considers the implications of evolving file types, and delves into the philosophical question of whether all data should be preserved.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strengthening Relationships Weakened By The Internet</title>
      <link>https://strangelabs.io/blog/strengthening-relationships-weakened-by-the-internet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://strangelabs.io/blog/strengthening-relationships-weakened-by-the-internet/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Back in 2003, whilst I was a teenager, I found myself rebelling against the idea of owning a mobile phone. Something about it just didn’t sit right with me. I think that I sensed a future where increased social connections would lead to each one feeling less meaningful. Or maybe it was simply the reluctance to be available 24/7. I cherished the ritual of asking my parents to use the house phone, ensuring no one was online, and then calling a friend’s landline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EGX Rezzed 2019 - Our most interesting picks!</title>
      <link>https://strangelabs.io/blog/egx-rezzed-2019-best-of-the-bunch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://strangelabs.io/blog/egx-rezzed-2019-best-of-the-bunch/</guid>
      <description>EGX Rezzed, London’s biggest gaming event, concluded a week ago. Strange Labs was in attendance and amongst the various qualities of cosplayers wandering around, excellent merchandise and endless games to play, there were also some pretty cool talks from the developers themselves. We managed to get to a few (annoyingly everything inevitably overlaps at these sorts of events) and thought we would share our favourite picks of brand new, up and coming games.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Designing A Space For Technology Enthusiasts</title>
      <link>https://strangelabs.io/blog/designing-a-space-for-technology-enthusiasts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://strangelabs.io/blog/designing-a-space-for-technology-enthusiasts/</guid>
      <description>Introduction From 2017 to 2020, I embarked on an exciting project to transform my traditional PC repair shop into a dynamic social space where programmers could meet, collaborate, and work on projects. Midway through this transformation, I shared an update on the progress. Now, as we close the chapter on this journey, I’m reflecting on the design process and what we achieved. For the final look before closing, be sure to check out the photos at the end.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Code, Data And Understanding Each Other In A Digital World</title>
      <link>https://strangelabs.io/blog/code-data-and-understanding-each-other/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://strangelabs.io/blog/code-data-and-understanding-each-other/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Our understanding of one another can only ever approximate true comprehension. We cannot inhabit each other&amp;rsquo;s consciousness to experience the world as the other does. Knowing that no one will ever truly understand you, how does that influence your experiences? We must dedicate time to learning each other&amp;rsquo;s stories and remain open-minded to align our understanding as closely as possible. This is already a challenge in our physical lives, but what happens in the digital realm?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arguing For Open Source</title>
      <link>https://strangelabs.io/blog/arguing-for-open-source/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://strangelabs.io/blog/arguing-for-open-source/</guid>
      <description>Why Should We Trust What People Hide from Us? Open source technology holds the potential to build greater trust among people. By extending the principles of open source from computer science to other areas of society and culture, we might unlock significant benefits.&#xA;What is open source? At its core, open source refers to software whose source code, the underlying instructions that define how the software functions, is freely available for anyone to view, modify, and redistribute.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Full Stack Buildings Design</title>
      <link>https://strangelabs.io/blog/full-stack-buildings-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://strangelabs.io/blog/full-stack-buildings-design/</guid>
      <description>Designing Buildings in the Future The future of architecture is evolving, giving rise to a new breed of architects with broader vision, deeper influence, and a more comprehensive understanding of their craft. These future architects won’t just design buildings in the traditional sense, from material selection to philosophical considerations, but will also grasp the intricacies of modern technology. They will understand everything from the flow of electrons in wiring to the connectivity of the internet, and how these elements interact with the building&amp;rsquo;s users in an increasingly digital world.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
